demandforced3.com 2016-05-26

# Automated Marketing Solution - Online Reputation Management & Appointment Scheduling by Demandforce

Demandforce is committed to protecting your privacy.

Therefore, we want to communicate openly and directly with each and every Demandforce user whenever possible.

The Demandforce Privacy policy affects three groups of users: Demandforce subscribers, the customers of Demandforce subscribers ("consumers") and visitors to our corporate website. Collectively, these groups are referred to as "users".

We treat our users' information as if it were our own personal information.

**Demandforce does not sell, share or rent our users' personally identifiable information unless required by law.**

**Demandforce does not send e-mail or other communications without user permission.**

**Demandforce does not send spam.**

**We stand committed to being vigilant as to your continued privacy and constantly improving our service.**

### Demandforce Subscribers

Demandforce asks new subscribers to provide their name, business name, address, phone and fax numbers and e-mail address. We call this "Subscriber Information". As a new subscriber, you will also be asked to provide payment information such as a credit card or bank account number, which is used for monthly billing purposes only. As part of Demandforce's service deployment process, your customers' personally identifiable information ("Consumer Information") is uploaded into our secure servers. This process is performed so Demandforce can provide our services to consumers on your behalf. The collection of Subscriber Information and Consumer Information is done solely to provide our services to you in accordance with your Subscriber Agreement and Terms of Use.

### Consumer information (Your customer information)

Demandforce will not use Consumer Information for the purposes of directly marketing to, or otherwise communicating directly with those consumers about Demandforce or any third party products or services.

### Consumers

As a consumer, you receive valuable and timely communication, including reminders and "Thank You" notes from a company with which you have an existing business relationship. You have the right at any time to opt-out from receiving these communications. If you would like to opt-out from receiving these communications please e-mail[privacy@Demandforce.com](mailto:privacy@Demandforce.com), click on the "preferences" button in our emails, or sending "STOP" in response to text messages. You acknowledge that if you transmit personal health information you waive any right to the privacy of such information.

### Corporate website visitors

Visitors to Demandforce website can provide personal information in order to receive further information about our services.

## How Demandforce collects personally identifiable information

Demandforce collects personal information from users within our website and hosted product. This enables Demandforce to provide users with better information about our services. Providing your information to Demandforce ensures that a visit to our site or hosted service is simple, convenient and productive.

Demandforce does not sell, share or rent user information in ways that differ from what is disclosed in this statement, requested by the user or a legal requirement.

### Log files

As is true of most websites, Demandforce gathers certain information automatically and stores it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser types, page views, referring URL and a date/time stamp.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small text file containing a unique identification number that is transferred from a web server to the end user's computer. Cookies allow us to personalize your experience with our website and to ensure that no unauthorized users can access our subscribers' web pages within our service. We do not issue any cookies which enable third parties to track the activities of end users.

### Response to subpoenas and other legal requests.

Demandforce may disclose, access, or report personal information when we believe, in good faith, we're required to do so by law or to protect our legal rights. We may also do this in connection with an investigation into a suspected violation involving a Terms of Service, fraud, intellectual property infringement, or other activity that may be illegal or expose us to legal liability. For example, we may be required to disclose personal information to cooperate with regulators or law enforcement authorities or to comply with a court order, subpoena, search warrant, or law enforcement request.

## How Demandforce may use the information

Demandforce does collect and aggregate (bring together) broad demographic information that we may use in different ways:

Demandforce may sell or share with our partners and advertisers non-identifiable aggregated demographic information compiled from Subscriber Information and/or Consumer Information.

Demandforce may use Subscriber Information and/or Consumer Information to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track user's movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. This information may also be used for the purpose of monitoring and tracking use of our hosted site in order to improve product delivery to our subscribers.

### Choice and Opt-Out

Demandforce always provides the ability for Subscriber and Consumers to opt-out of having personally identifiable information used as part of our service offering. All e-mails and text messages Demandforce sends out on behalf of our subscribers provide a way for consumers to opt-out. In addition, any visitor to our site, subscriber to our service or consumer may e-mail us at [privacy@Demandforce.com](mailto:privacy@Demandforce.com) to opt-out of receiving any further correspondence from us.

### Links to other sites

This website contains links to other sites. Demandforce is not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. When you leave our site, we encourage you to read the privacy statements of each and every website that you visit to review their use of personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected at Demandforce's website and its hosted service.

### Updating personally identifiable information

Subscribers to our service may update their personal information or their customers' personal information by logging into their home page on our hosted product site. Our software is configured to synchronize Consumer Information on a regular basis with the related subscriber's consumer database, so any updates, changes or opt-out requests communicated directly to our subscribers by their consumers will be automatically uploaded into our site, keeping our site up-to-date with current and correct Consumer Information.

### Security

Demandforce takes the highest precautions to protect our subscribers' information. When you submit sensitive information via the corporate website or our hosted product, your information is protected both online and offline using standard security best practices such as firewalls, encryption and intrusion detection. Full backups are performed every week on the entire file system and incremental backups are done daily. Finally, all hosted servers are kept physically secure in world-class data centers.

## Sale of Our Business

If we sell, merge or transfer any part of our business, part of the sale may include your personal information. If so, you will be asked if you'd like to stop receiving promotional information following any change of control.

## Changes to this privacy policy

Demandforce will update this policy from time to time. A "last revised" date will always be included at the top of the statement. To keep up-to-date with Demandforce's privacy policy, please check this page periodically.

## Contact information

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or if you feel that Demandforce is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you can contact us by e-mailing your questions or concerns to [privacy@Demandforce.com](mailto:privacy@Demandforce.com) or mail us at 22 Fourth Street, 12th Floor, San Francisco, CA 94104.

© 2016 Demandforce Inc. All rights reserved. _May 18, 2012_
